ebaumsworld.com 2018-12-31

# Funny Pictures, Funny Videos | eBaum's World | eBaum's World

**PRIVACY POLICY**

_Last updated: August 12, 2018_

Viumbe, LLC. (" **Viumbe** " or “ **Company** ”) respects your privacy. This privacy policy (“ **Privacy Policy** ”) explains the privacy practices of Viumbe in connection with the users (" **you** ", " **your** " or " **user** ") access or use of the following websites owned and operated by Viumbe and included therein: EbaumsWorld.com, YourDailyMedia.com, and Celebremix.com (together will be referred to as: " **Site** " or “ **Website** ”) and Viumbe's products, mobile apps, software, data feeds, and services offered to you on, from or through the Viumbe Sites (collectively the " **Service** "). The Privacy Policy describes the ways Viumbe collects, processes and uses your Personal Information (as defined below) when using the Service and the rights and options available to you with respect to your information. 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at: [contact@viumbe.com](mailto:contact@viumbe.com).

We have included below information about which data is collected, how we process and use your data, but before, we would like to explain the basis on which we do so: 

i. Where a user registers for our Services, we process such Personal Information in order to perform our contract with the user; 

ii. When visitors access our Site, we collect certain online identifiers which we have a legitimate interest in processing such data; 

iii. For direct marketing to our users we have legitimate interest to process such data; or 

iv. We (or our third parties) may also process your Personal Information where you have provided us with consent to do so (such as by providing consent to cookies placed on the Site).

**1. ****WHAT TYPE OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT?**

Depending on your interaction with us (meaning, if you are just browsing our Site, or if you have registered to our Services and opened an account, etc.), we may collect two types of information you, as follows:

  * Non Personal Information: The _first type_ of information is non-identifiable information which may be made available or gathered through your use of the Services. To clarify, we are not aware of your identity due to such information (“ **Non-Personal Information** ”).

  * Personal Information: The _second type_ of information is individually identifiable information, namely information that identifies an individual or may with reasonable effort identify an individual (“ **Personal Information** ”).

In the event we combine Personal Information with Non-Personal Information, the combined information will be treated as Personal __ Information for as long as it remains combined.

**_Information we collect from and how we use it:_**

**Type of Information**

| 

**How Do We Use It?**  
  
---|---  
  
aggregated usage information and technical information transmitted or automatically collected such as (but not limited to): type of browser and the settings, operating system, type of the device used to access our Services, your ISP, log data, visits to the Site, pages viewed, items views or items saved, date and time stamp, duration on the page, approximate geographical location and the path taken in the Site.

| 

We use this technical data in order to operate and manage our Services.   
  
In the event you [**contact us**](http://www.ebaumsworld.com/pages/contact/) for support or other inquiries by sending us an email you will provide us with your name, phone number and email address.

| 

We will use this information solely for the purpose of responding to your inquiries and provide you with the support or information you have requested.   
  
In the event you will wish to **comment, like or share a post through the Service,** you will be required to open an account, during the registration you will provide us with your username and email address and will be required to create a password, at which time you thereby represent and warrant that you are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your details and password. You represent and warrant that you will not provide us with inaccurate, misleading or false information.

You may also choose to sign in with a social network account that may provide us with access to certain information about you as stored therein (e.g. full name, e-mail and any other information which you made public).

_Note , you are not required to create an account to view the posts or activities within the Site. _

| 

We will use this information for the purpose of performing our contract with you, provide you with the Services you have requested (e.g. allow you to comment on a post, etc.).   
  
IP Address: we may collect certain identifiers such as your IP addresses, and precise location solely through the mobile app in the event you have consented to provide us with your location. Note that, while these identifiers are considered personally identifiable information in many jurisdictions (such as the EEA), there are some jurisdictions in which such data sets are not considered as Personal Data. Therefore, we treat such information as Personal Data, in accordance with applicable laws. The data collected may be also stored on your device. Please see opt – out options below.

| 

We (directly or by third party service providers as detailed below) may collect our visitors’ IP. We use this for our legitimate interests of operating, providing, maintaining, protecting, managing, customizing and improving our Site and Services and the way in which we offer them and our legitimate interests of auditing and tracking usage statistics and traffic flow.  
  
We may collect certain precise location, provided that you enable the “Location Services” on your device. Once the user confirms the access to its geolocation data, such access will always be allowed when user visits or use the app, unless you turn off the Location Services on your device.

| 

You may voluntarily consent to providing Company with your precise location.   
  
User Generated Content: You may upload your personal information to the Service and share the information with Viumbe and users of the Service. The personal details that you upload, including any materials, videos, sound recordings, compositions, pictures, song lyrics, text, software, scripts, graphics, photos, videos, audiovisual combinations, interactive features and other materials you may view on, access through, or contribute to the Service (" **Content** "), may be accessible to other users and may appear in search results on the Service. PLEASE USE CAUTION AND COMMON SENSE WHEN YOU UPLOAD YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION, ESPECIALLY ANY PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION. 

The content that you upload to the Service is not private.

| 

You voluntarily consent to upload and make the Content public.   
  
If you voluntarily **subscribe to our newsletter** or agreed to receive the newsletter during your registration, you will be asked to provide us with your email address. You can unsubscribe at any time using the unsubscribe option within the body of the newsletter or by contacting our data protection officer at: [dpo@viumble.com](mailto:dpo@viumble.com)

| 

We will use your email address in order to send you information related to our Services and to keep you up to date regarding new Services. We may also contact you to ensure the details you provided us are accurate (i.e., during registration) and to get your feedback on you purchase (if applicable).   
  
**2. ****HOW WE COLLECT INFORMATION**

Depending on the nature of your interaction with the Services, we may collect information as follows:

  * Automatically – we may use cookies (as elaborated in the Cookies Section below) to gather some information automatically.
  * Provided by you voluntarily – we will collect information if and when you choose to provide us with the information, such as through a registration process, contact us communications, sign-up to our newsletter, etc. We may collect two types of information from you.

**3. ****COOKIES AND ADVERTISING CAMPAIGNS**

Viumbe may use cookies on the Service. Cookies are packets of information sent by the Service's servers to your web browser and then sent back by the browser each time it accesses the Service's servers. The cookies may contain a variety of information, such as the content of search queries, the Service's pages you have accessed, session durations and IP addresses. 

The Service may use cookies for various purposes, such as to save you the need to re-enter your user name and password each time you log-in on the Service, to facilitate the use of services on the Service, to collect statistical information with respect to the use of the Service, to verify information, to customize Service to your personal preferences and for information security purposes. Some of the cookies may expire when the session ends and you exit your browser. Other cookies are saved on your computer’s hard drive. If you wish to block the Service's cookies, then please use the help button in your browser and follow the necessary instructions. However, bear in mind that disabling cookies may complicate or even prevent your use of the Service, or certain features thereof. You can find more information about cookies at [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/) . You may remove our cookie by following the instructions of your device preferences; however, if you choose to disable our cookie, some features of our Service may not operate properly and your online experience may be limited. You may control how your browser responds to cookies by adjusting the privacy and security settings of your web browser.

Viumbe permits third party advertising companies to place advertisements on Viumbe Services and manage their display. In order to manage the advertisements, these companies post cookies on your computer and embed web beacons in the advertisements or in Viumbe Websites' pages. Web beacons are tiny graphics with unique identifiers, embedded in web pages and used to assist in collecting information about the sites usage. The collected information may identify you, and is only intended to match the displayed advertisements to your personal interests. The use of cookies and web beacons by advertising companies is subject to their own privacy policies and not to this Privacy Policy. Such companies have no access to Viumbe's Websites' cookies and Viumbe has no access to their cookies. 

Should you wish to check the privacy policies of the companies that are managing the advertising scheme on Viumbe Websites, you may do so through the table we provided below. 

To receive further information about the advertising companies that Viumbe works with, please contact us at: [contact@viumbe.com](mailto:contact@viumbe.com).   

**Cookie**

| 

**Purpose**

| 

**Privacy Policy and Opt-Out**  
  
---|---|---  
  
**Facebook**

| 

Enable use of the Service and Advertising 

| 

**Google**

| 

Analytic Purposes and Advertising 

| 

To opt out of Google's "interest-based ads" and to learn more about Google's collection of your personal information to serve ads in connection with Viumbe Websites, click [here](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/)  
  
**Twitter**

| 

Optimization of the Services

| 

[https://twitter.com/en/privacy](https://twitter.com/en/privacy) __  
  
**OpenX**

| 

Advertising 

| 

**DistrictM**

| 

Advertising 

| 

**AppNexus**

| 

Advertising 

| 

**Rubicon**

| 

Advertising 

| 

[https://rubiconproject.com/rubicon-project-yield-optimization-privacy-policy/](https://rubiconproject.com/rubicon-project-yield-optimization-privacy-policy/)  
  
**Ora.tv**

| 

Advertising 

| 

**33Across**

| 

Advertising 

| 

**bRealTime**

| 

Advertising 

| 

**Amazon**

| 

Advertising 

| 

[https://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html?nodeId=468496](https://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html?nodeId=468496)  
  
**Civic Science**

| 

Optimization of the Service and Advertising 

| 

**Chart Beat**

| 

Optimization of the Service

| 

**Crazy Egg**

| 

Optimization of the Service

| 

**Deployads**

| 

Optimization of the Service and Advertising 

| 

**DoubleClick**

| 

Optimization of the Service and Advertising 

| 

Exponential Interactive, Inc.

| 

Advertising

| 

As our partner, Exponential Interactive have a legitimate interest to collect and profile personal data in the form of IP address and cookie ID from users on our website in order to provide targeted online advertising and ad measurement. For more details including opt-out requests, access requests or complaints, please review their privacy policy or contact their data protection officer via [privacy@exponential.com](mailto:privacy@exponential.com)  
  
**Nativo**

| 

Advertising 

| 

**Connatix**

| 

Advertising 

| 

**Oath**

| 

Advertising 

| 

**ShareThrough**

| 

Advertising 

| 

**SourcePoint**

| 

Optimization of the Service

| 

**Spot.IM**

| 

Advertising 

| 

We may use spot.im for targeted advertising, for more information please see Spot.im privacy policy available [here](http://www.spot.im/privacy).  
  
**Arrowchat**

| 

Optimization of the Service

| 

**Ebaumsworld** **Cookies**

| 

Enable the use of the Site and Service and Analytics 

|   
  
**4. ****SHARING INFORMATION WITH OTHERS**

We do not sell, trade, or rent users' Personal Information to other parties. We may share information solely in the following events: 

  * When you use the Service, or when you take part in any content-related activity. In these cases, the Service will share your information to the extent necessary to facilitate your use of the Service;
  * If Viumbe reasonably believes that you have breached the Service's Terms of Service, or abused your rights to use the Service, or performed any act or omission that Viumbe reasonably believes to be violating any applicable law, rules, or regulations. Viumbe may share your information in these cases, with law enforcement and other competent authorities and with any third party, as may be required to handle any result of your wrongdoing;
  * If Viumbe is required, or reasonably believes that it is required by law and/or law enforcement agencies to share or disclose your information; 
  * In any case of dispute, or legal proceeding of any kind between you and Viumbe or between you and other users with respect to, or in relation with the Service; 
  * To operate the Service and Viumbe’s services, to send messages, and to provide search results and links;
  * In any case where Viumbe reasonably believes that sharing information is necessary to prevent imminent physical damage or damage to property;
  * If Viumbe organizes the operation of the Service within a different framework, or through another legal structure or entity, or if Viumbe is acquired by, or merged into or with another entity, provided however, that those entities agree to be bound by the provisions of this policy, with respective changes taken into consideration;
  * Viumbe may also share personally identifiable information with companies or organizations connected, or affiliated with Viumbe, such as subsidiaries, sister-companies and parent companies, and other partners, with the express provision that their use of such information must comply with this policy. 
  * Identifiers **-** we may disclose or share identifiers collected by us (as detailed above), for the purpose of operating our business and providing the Services, as well as **** to **** calculate payments and detect fraud, security or technical issues in connection with the Service;

**5. ****DATA RETENTION**

We retain the Non-Personal Information we collect for as long as needed to provide the Service, carry out our business purpose, perform our contract with you, and to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements, in accordance and compliance with applicable laws, or until an individual request us to delete its Personal Information, as detailed above, but not longer than 24 months in an identifiable form, or as required by law. 

Please note that unless you decide to delete your User Account by sending us a request do so, or any part thereof, or instruct us otherwise, we retain the information we collect for as long as needed to perform the above. Once you delete your Account you will not be able to recover it and will have to register again with a new account in case you choose to use the Service.

In addition, some of the data we receive depends on your privacy settings with the social network (i.e., Facebook) and you should always review, and if necessary, adjust your privacy settings on third-party websites and services before linking or connecting them to our Site.

We are entitled to rectify, replenish or remove incomplete or inaccurate information, at any time and at our sole discretion.

**6. ****CHOICE**

**_Mobile Opt-out:_**

Android-[https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922](https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922) _or_ iOS– [https://support.apple.com/en-il/HT205223](https://support.apple.com/en-il/HT205223).

**_Website Opt-out:_**

You may control how your browser responds to cookies by adjusting the privacy and security settings of your web browser.

Please refer to the support page of the browser you are using. In this regard, following are some links which you may find useful: 

  * Google Chrome: [https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en); 
  * Firefox: [https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences); 
  * Internet Explorer: [https://support.microsoft.com/en-gb/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookies](https://support.microsoft.com/en-gb/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookies); 
  * Safari: [https://support.apple.com/kb/PH21411](https://support.apple.com/kb/PH21411); 
  * Edge: [https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/windows-10-microsoft-edge-and-privacy (Edge)](https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/windows-10-microsoft-edge-and-privacy%20\(Edge\)); 
  * Opera: [http://www.opera.com/help/tutorials/security/cookies/ ](http://www.opera.com/help/tutorials/security/cookies/%20\(Opera\)); 

**_Industry Standards_**

You may opt out of certain advertisers’ cookies and browser-enabled, interest-based advertising at the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) website- [NAI consumer opt-out](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/#/) and the Digital Advertising Alliance’s (“DAA”) website- [DAA opt-out page](http://www.aboutads.info/). If you wish to opt out of interest-based advertising, you may click [here](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/). Please note you will continue to receive generic ads.

**_Contact us_**

You may also Contact Us at: [contact@viumbe.com](mailto:contact@viumbe.com) and we will be happy to assist you. Note that once you opt out, part of the Services provided by us might no longer be available and some features may not work if you revoke the data transfer.

In the event, that you have any additional complaints about your privacy rights, please initially contact the Data Protection Officer. Please note that you have the right at any time to contact your local data protection authority.

**7. ****USER RIGHTS**

Individuals have the right to know what information we hold about them and, in some cases, to have such information communicated to them. Individuals may also ask for our confirmation as to whether or not we process their Personal Information. Subject to the limitations in applicable law, individuals may also be entitled to obtain from us the Personal Information they have provided to us in a structured, commonly-used, and machine-readable format, and may have the right to transmit such Personal Information to another party.

The principal rights under applicable data protection law in relation to Personal Information are as follows: the right to access any information which is provided to us; the right to rectification; the right to erasure; the right to restrict processing; the right to object to processing; the right to data portability; the right to complain to a supervisory authority; and the right to withdraw consent (to the extent applicable).

We provide you with the ability to exercise certain choices and controls in connection with our treatment of your Personal Information, depending on your relationship with us. For more information, please review our user right policy and online forms available at: [www.ebaumsworld.com/user-rights](http://www.ebaumsworld.com/user-rights). 

If you wish to exercise any or all of the above rights, please either use the dashboard of your account or please download our user right form and send it to our Data Protection Officer at: [dpo@viumbe.com](mailto:dpo@viumbe.com).

Where we are not able to provide you with the information for which you have asked, we will endeavor to explain the reasoning for this and inform you of your rights, including the right to complain to the supervisor authority. We reserve the right to ask for reasonable evidence to verify your identity before we provide you with any such information in accordance with applicable law. In addition, the process of locating and deleting the data may take up to one (1) month (following the receipt of the validation proof we require) in accordance with applicable law. 

Data privacy and related laws in your jurisdiction may provide you with different or additional rights related to the data we collect from you, which may also apply.

**8. ****IMPORTANT NOTICE ABOUT CHILDREN'S PRIVACY**

You represent and warrant that, (i) if you are located in the US, you are at least 13 years of age; or if you are located in any other GEO, you are above the age defined as “child” under applicable laws in your jurisdiction (collectively “ **Child** ” or “ **Children** ”); and (ii) you are of legal competence to enter into this Privacy Policy. If you are under 18, please be sure to read the terms of this Privacy Policy with your parents or legal guardians. The Services are not directed or intended for Children, as defined under applicable law, and we do not knowingly collect or solicit information from children. If we obtain actual knowledge that a User is considered as a Child under applicable law, we will take steps to immediately delete such User’s Personal Information. If you become aware or have any reason to believe that a Child has shared any information with us, please contact us at: [contact@viumbe.com  
](mailto:contact@viumbe.com)Provisions relevant to Non U.S. users

We may store or process your information in the United States or in other countries. If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (" **EEA** ") we will take appropriate measures to ensure that your information receives an adequate level of data protection upon its transfer outside of the EEA. If you are a resident of a jurisdiction where transfer of your data requires your consent, then your consent to this Privacy Policy includes your express consent for such transfer of your Personal Information. 

**9. ****INFORMATION SECURITY**

Your privacy is very important to the Company and therefore we are committed to protecting your Personal Information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. We have implemented physical, technical and administrative security measures for the Services that comply with applicable laws and industry standards. For more information please see: [www.viumbe.com/security](http://www.viumbe.com/security)

Company seeks to minimize the amount of data that it stores on its servers in the first place. If you feel that your privacy was treated not in accordance with our policy, or if any person attempted gain unauthorized access to the Personal Information please contact us at: [contact@viumbe.com](mailto:contact@viumbe.com).

Further, in the event of a data incident, in which we discover your Personal Information may be at risk, then we will take reasonable efforts to notify you and the applicable authority (if required, subject to applicable laws).

**10. ****CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

Viumbe may from time to time change the terms of this Privacy Policy. Substantial changes will take effect 7 days after Viumbe has posted an initial notification on the Service's homepage or any other relevant web pages on the Service, with respect to such changes. Other changes will take effect immediately after their initial posting on the Service, unless Viumbe amends the Terms to comply with legal requirements. In such cases the amendments will become effective immediately upon their initial posting, or as required.  
You agree to be bound by any of the changes made in the terms of this policy. Continuing to use the Service will indicate your acceptance of the amended terms. If you do not agree with any of the amended terms, you must avoid any further use of the Service.   

**11. ****DO NOT TRACK DISCLOSURE**

Our Service does not respond to Do Not Track signals. For more information about Do Not Track signals, please see: [http://www.allaboutdnt.com/](http://www.allaboutdnt.com/).

**12. ****CONTACT VIUMBE**

You may send Viumbe requests, responses, questions and complaints, by contacting Viumbe at [contact@viumbe.com](mailto:contact@viumbe.com), or by post mail to:  
Viumbe, LLC  
1550 Bryant St., Suite 470  
San Francisco, CA 94103.

**13. ****DATA PROTECTION OFFICER**

If you have any requests regarding the data collected under this Privacy Policy, including without limitation, requests to remove, delete, amend, modify or transfer the data, please contact our Data Protection Officer at: [dpo@viumble.com](mailto:dpo@viumble.com)

Please be sure to include your information in any correspondence to us so that we can respond to your inquiry in a timely manner.
